# **Rachel Paltiel**

0526110245

Rachel.paltiel21@gmail.com Ramat Gan



## In Short

Full Stack Developer specialized in C#, Typescript, asp.net and angular

Passionate about technology and love learning new techniques, methods, and languages to accomplish my current goal.

Autodidact and creative when comes to solving problems and developing new solutions.

Searching for a fulltime long term software dev position, with Agile practices and a quiet geeky team.

# **Experience**

## **Full stack Software Developer** 01/2023 - Now | Ewave Mobile

- Developed multiple projects from scratch using C#, asp.net and angular
- Compiled and configured projects to desktop apps as well as web applications
- Created SQL Server Jobs and complicated procedures maintaining sufficient data storage, transfer and digest while preserving user-friendly response time
- Acquired knowledge about cyber security, preforming penetration testing (using Burp Suite) and implementing methods for data protection
- Appreciates an appealing, intuitive, and user-friendly interface and will invest the effort and time to achieve that
- Another thing here

#### **QA Tester**

## 06/2022 - 01/2023 | Elad Health

- Full-time QA tester, worked on a C# based system and SQL DataBase
- Ran procedures, queries and tested different functions using SQL server (Microsoft)
- Assigned with a VB.Net API project, a system that served both the QA team and the Dev team
- Worked in a QA team with daily interactions with the Developers and DBA
- Jenkins and TFS were the main tools we worked with

## **Projects**



## **Skills**

#### **Programming Languages**

- C#
- JS
- TS
- HTML
- **CSS**

#### **Development Frameworks**

- **Angular**
- ASP.NET
- Ionic

#### **DataBase**

- **MSSQL**
- MySQL
- MongoDB

## Tools

- Visual Studio & VSCode
- GIT, BitBucket, SVN
- Jira
- Azure (TFS)
- Monday
- Swagger
- **Postman**
- **Burp Suite**

## Languages

- **English Native**
- Hebrew Native

# QA Tester

#### 06/2020 - 06/2022 | Finbot

- Promoted to Product Manager and was sent to study Data System Analytics
- Studied SQL, C#, HTML, CSS, JavaScript in the Technion and built a web application based on those technologies
- Git and Jira were the tools we worked with, in an Agile environment
- Promoted to QA from Tech Support after proving my value and knowledge of web applications and technologies (self-taught)
- Learned to use the tools around me to meet requirements and achieve team goals (Google Dev Tools, Git, Google Analytics and more)

# QA Tester 11/2019 – 06/2020 | MYHR

- First step in the Startup world, where I discovered the wonders of technology
- Agile mindset and work methodology were rooted to me from the start
- Promoted to QA from Payroll Accounting to test a Fintech web application, took up 40% off my job
- Jira Software was the tool we used to manage our work items

## **Education**

System Analysis
2021 - now | Technion
Payroll Accountant, Bookkeeper
2016 - 2018 | BDO
High School Graduate
2014 - 2016 | Hila

## **Outside the office**

- Hackathon Enthusiast
- Kali Linux adherent
- Motorcycles